TINA - Theoretical Investigations in Network Analysis

This serves as a catalog of various coding projects involving network strucutre and metrics, acting both as an 
easy way for me to show examples of my code and to become familiar with the github environment.

1. **Effect of Sampling Completeness on Network Metrics**

This project is through the Novak lab, in which I use species acculmulation curves from the
Kelp Forest database to analyze the effects of sampling completeness on various metrics.  